export const questions = [
    { "questionID": 1, 
  "questionText": "A 30% loss on cost price is what percent loss on selling price?",
   "choices": ["30%",
    "20%",
    "15%",
    "None of these",
    ],
    "answer": "None of these" },

    { "questionID": 2, 
  "questionText": "A, B and C hire a taxi for Rs. 2400 for one day. A, B and C used the car for 6 hours, 8 hours and 10 hours respectively. How much did C pay?",
   "choices": ["Rs. 800",
    "Rs. 1000",
    "Rs. 600",
    "Rs. 1200"],
    "answer": "Rs. 1000" },

    { "questionID": 3, 
  "questionText": "The ratio of investments of A and B is 8 : 7 and the ratio of their yearend profits is 20 : 21. If B invested for 12 months, then find the period of investment of A:",
   "choices": ["6 months",
    "8 months",
    "10 months",
    "12 months"],
    "answer": "10 months" },

    { "questionID": 4, 
  "questionText": "What percent is 2 minutes 24 seconds of an hour?",
   "choices": ["6%",
    "2%",
    "4%",
    "8%"],
    "answer": "4%" },

    { "questionID": 5, 
  "questionText": "Evaluate: 3 cos 80° cosec 10° + 2 cos 59° cosec 31°",
   "choices": ["1",
    "2",
    "3",
    "5"],
    "answer": "5" },

    { "questionID": 6, 
  "questionText": "The total cost of 8 buckets and 5 mugs is Rs. 92 and the total cost of 5 buckets and 8 mugs is Rs. 77. Find the cost of 2 mugs and 3 buckets.",
   "choices": ["35",
    "70",
    "30",
    "38"],
    "answer": "35" },

    { "questionID": 7, 
  "questionText": "If 4x/3 + 2P = 12 for what value of P, x = 6?",
   "choices": ["6",
    "4",
    "2",
    "1"],
    "answer": "2" },

    { "questionID": 8, 
  "questionText": "What number must be added to the expression 16a2 – 12a to make it a perfect square?",
   "choices": ["9/4",
    "11/2",
    "13/2",
    "16"],
    "answer": "9/4" },

    { "questionID": 9, 
  "questionText": "The straight line 2x + 3y = 12 passes through:",
   "choices": ["1st, 2nd and 3rd quadrant",
    "1st, 2nd and 4th quadrant",
    "2nd, 3rd and 4th quadrant",
    "1st, 3rd and 4th quadrant"],
    "answer": "1st, 2nd and 4th quadrant" },

    { "questionID": 10, 
  "questionText": "In ΔABC, ∠A + ∠B = 65°, ∠B + ∠C = 140°, then find ∠B.",
   "choices": ["40",
    "25",
    "35",
    "40"],
    "answer": "25" },

    { "questionID": 11, 
  "questionText": "If 4x - 3y = 19 and x + 2y = 13, what are the respective values of x and y?",
   "choices": ["5, 4",
    "6, 5",
    "7, 3",
    "8, 7"],
    "answer": "7, 3" },

    { "questionID": 12, 
  "questionText": "Due to global recession starting in January, Ram's monthly salary of Rs 8,000 was cut by 10%. The monthly expenses, which were Rs 6,000, increased at the rate of 5% per month. From which month will he have no savings if the recession lasted for a year?",
   "choices": ["May",
    "April",
    "March",
    "June"],
    "answer": "April" },

    { "questionID": 13, 
  "questionText": "A hemispherical bowl is 176 cm round the brim. Supposing it to be half full, how many persons may be served from it in hemispherical glasses with diameter of 4 cm at the top?",
   "choices": ["1372",
    "1272",
    "1172",
    "1472"],
    "answer": "1372" },

    { "questionID": 14, 
  "questionText": "A and B working together can complete a piece of work in 12 days. B and C working together can complete the same work in 16 days. A worked at it for 5 days and B worked at it for 7 days. C finished the remaining work in 13 days. How many days would C alone take to complete it?",
   "choices": ["32",
    "24",
    "10",
    "40"],
    "answer": "24" },

    { "questionID": 15, 
  "questionText": "Sixteen men can complete a work in twelve days. Twenty-four children can complete the same work in eighteen days. Twelve men and eight children started working and after eight days three more children joined them. How many days will they now take to complete the remaining work?",
   "choices": ["6",
    "4",
    "2",
    "None of these"],
    "answer": "4" },

    { "questionID": 16, 
  "questionText": "Two men A and B working together complete a piece of work which it would have taken them 30 and 40 days respectively to complete if they worked separately. If they received a payment of ` 21,000, B's share is",
   "choices": ["8000",
    "12000",
    "9000",
    "10000"],
    "answer": "9000" },

    { "questionID": 17, 
  "questionText": "If Rs 10 be allowed as true discount on a bill of Rs 110 due at the end of a certain time, then the discount allowed on the sum due at the end of double the time is",
   "choices": ["22",
    "21.81",
    "20",
    "18.33"],
    "answer": "20" },

    { "questionID": 18, 
  "questionText": "A man purchased a cycle for Rs 3,000 and sold it the same day for Rs 3,600, allowing the buyer a credit of 2 years. If the rate of interest be 10% per annum, then the man has a gain of",
   "choices": ["7.5%",
    "5%",
    "20%",
    "None of these"],
    "answer": "None of these" },

    { "questionID": 19, 
  "questionText": "The angle of elevation on the top of a tower from two horizontal points at distance of 'a' and 'b' metres from the tower are 'α' and '90 -α ' respectively. The height of the tower will be (where a > b)",
   "choices": ["ab metres",
  "√ ab metres",
  "√ a/b metres",
  "√ b/a metres",],
    "answer": "√ ab metres" },

    { "questionID": 20, 
  "questionText": "A person observes the angle of elevation of a building as 30°. The person proceeds towards the building with a speed of 25(√ 3 -1)m/hour. After 2 hours, he observes the angle of elevation as 45°. The height of the building (in m) is",
   "choices": ["50 ( √ 3 +1)",
  "50",
  "100",
  "50 ( √ 3 -1)", ],
    "answer": "B1" },

    { "questionID": 21, 
  "questionText": "7 cannibals of XYZ island, decide to throw a party. As you may be aware, cannibals are guys who eat human beings. The senior among them – Father Cannibal decides that any 6 of them will eat up one cannibal, then out of the remaining six – five of them will eat up one cannibal and so on till one is left. What is the time until one cannibal is left, if it takes one cannibal 3 hours to eat up one cannibal independently?",
   "choices": ["7 hrs 11 min",
"6 hrs 12 min",
"7 hrs 21 min",
"18 hrs 16 min",],
    "answer": "7 hrs 21 min" },

    { "questionID": 22, 
  "questionText": "Three articles are purchased for Rs. 1050, each with a different cost. The first article was sold at a loss of 20%, the second at 1/3rd gain and the third at 60% gain. Later he found that their SPs were same. What was his net gain/loss?",
   "choices": ["14.28% gain",
    "13% loss",
    "12% loss",
    "11.11% gain"],
    "answer": "14.28% gain" },

    { "questionID": 23, 
  "questionText": "In a game of tennis, A gives B 21 points and gives C 25 points. B gives C 10 points. How many points make the game?",
   "choices": ["50",
    "45",
    "35",
    "30"],
    "answer": "35" },

    { "questionID": 24, 
  "questionText": "A square, S1, circumscribes the circum circle of an equilateral triangle of side 10 cm. A square, S2, is inscribed in the in circle of the triangle. What is the ratio of the area of S1 to the area of S2?",
   "choices": ["4:1",
    "32:1",
    "8:1",
    "2:1"],
    "answer": "8:1" },

    { "questionID": 25, 
  "questionText": "A trader sells two bullocks for Rs. 8,400 each, neither losing nor gaining in total. If he sold one of the bullocks at a gain of 20%, the other is sold at a loss of",
   "choices": ["20%",
    "18%",
    "14%",
    "21%"],
    "answer": "20%" },
    
]

export const technicalQuestion = [
    { "questionID": 1, 
  "questionText": "What is the function of application programs in the DBMS approach?",
   "choices": ["processing functions",
  "storage functions",
  "access control",
  "None of these",],
    "answer": "processing functions" },

    { "questionID": 2, 
  "questionText": "What of the following sorting procedure is the slowest?",
   "choices": ["Bubble sort",
  "Quick sort",
  "Heap sort",
  "Shell sort",],
    "answer": "Bubble sort" },

    { "questionID": 3, 
  "questionText": "Which of the following is the function/s of the database administration?",
   "choices": ["Application checking",
"Database access planning",
"Computer applications management",
"All of these",],
    "answer": "B1" },

    { "questionID": 4, 
  "questionText": "What is the order to access the elements of a pushdown stack ?",
   "choices": ["First In First Out",
  "Last In First Out",
  "Last In Last Out",
  "First In Last Out",],
    "answer": "B1" },

    { "questionID": 5, 
  "questionText": "The C declaration int A[5][7] Contains x elements, each of these elements is itself an array containing y integers. What is the value of 2x+y",
   "choices": ["17",
    "24",
    "35",
    "None of these"],
    "answer": "17" },

    { "questionID": 6, 
  "questionText": `What is the output of the following code fragment?
int n= 4;
cout> > n++;
cout > > n;`,
   "choices": ["55",
    "44",
    "45",
    "None of these"],
    "answer": "45" },

    { "questionID": 7, 
  "questionText": "Which of the following command drops commands and tables from RDBMS ?",
   "choices": ["DROP",
  "LEAVE",
  "EXCLUDE",
  "STOP"],
    "answer": "DROP" },

    { "questionID": 8, 
  "questionText": "What is the use of cat command in Unix ?",
   "choices": ["It is used to delete files",
"It is used to display and create files",
"It is used to change or modify files",
"none of these" ],
    "answer": "It is used to display and create files" },

    { "questionID": 9, 
  "questionText": "Which of the following is not command of DML section of SQL ?",
   "choices": ["SELECT/FROM/WHERE",
  "INSERT INTO/VALUES",
  "UPDATE/SET/WHERE",
  "All of these", ],
    "answer": "All of these" },

    { "questionID": 10, 
  "questionText": "Which of the following is true regarding RIPv2?",
   "choices": ["It has a lower administrative distance than RIPv1.",
  "It converges faster than RIPv1.",
  "It has the same timers as RIPv1.",
  "It is harder to configure than RIPv1."],
    "answer": "It has the same timers as RIPv1." },

        { "questionID": 11, 
  "questionText": "The area in the main memory that can hold one page is called as ______",
   "choices": ["Page entry",
  "Page frame",
  "Frame",
  "Block",
  ],
    "answer": "Page frame" },

    { "questionID": 12, 
  "questionText": "The starting address of the page table is stored in ______",
   "choices": ["TLB",
  "R0",
  "Page table base register",
  "None of the above", ],
    "answer": "Page table base register" },

    { "questionID": 13, 
  "questionText": "Which one is true about clustered index?",
   "choices": ["Clustered index is not associated with table",
  "Clustered index is built by default on unique key columns",
  "Clustered index is not built on unique key columns",
  "None of the mentioned",],
    "answer": "Clustered index is built by default on unique key columns" },

    { "questionID": 14, 
  "questionText": "Does index take space in the disk?",
   "choices": ["It stores memory as and when required",
  "Yes, Indexes are stored on disk",
  "Indexes are never stored on disk",
  "Indexes take no space",],
    "answer": "Yes, Indexes are stored on disk" },

    { "questionID": 15, 
  "questionText": "Which of the following is not a characteristic of modern DBMS?",
   "choices": ["Real world entity",
  "More redundancy",
  "Isolation of data and applications",
  "Consistency",],
    "answer": "More redundancy" },

        { "questionID": 16, 
  "questionText": "What is the function of application programs in the DBMS approach?",
   "choices": ["To store data",
  "To process functions",
  "to access control",
  "all of the above", ],
    "answer": "To process functions" },

    { "questionID": 17, 
  "questionText": "Which of the following is the memory management supported in C++?",
   "choices": ["Static storage duration objects",
  "Automatic storage duration objects",
  "Thread storage duration objects",
  "All of these", ],
    "answer": "All of these" },

    { "questionID": 18, 
  "questionText": "Which is used to keep the call by reference value as unharmed?",
   "choices": ["static",
  "const",
  "absolute",
  "none of the mentioned",  ],
    "answer": "const" },

    { "questionID": 19, 
  "questionText": "What is meaning of following declaration? int(*ptr[5])();",
   "choices": ["ptr is pointer to function.",
  "ptr is pointer to array of function.",
  "ptr is pointer to such function which return type is array.",
  "ptr is pointer to array of function."],
    "answer": "ptr is pointer to array of function." },

    { "questionID": 20, 
  "questionText": "If the two networks having different protocols then the device used to communicate between these systems is",
   "choices": ["Bridge",
  "Repeater",
  "Hub",
  "Gateway", ],
    "answer": "B1" },

        { "questionID": 21, 
  "questionText": "Reference is__________",
   "choices": ["alias of an object",
  "used to rename an object",
  "a special operator",
  "a pointer to virtual function", ],
    "answer": "alias of an object" },

    { "questionID": 22, 
  "questionText": "Merge sort algorithm uses___________________technique",
   "choices": ["Brute force",
  "Dynamic programming",
  "Greedy",
  "Divide and conquer", ],
    "answer": "Divide and conquer" },

    { "questionID": 23, 
  "questionText": "The least frequently used (LFU) page replacement algorithm requires_________",
   "choices": ["the page with the smallest count to be replaced.",
  "the page with the longest count to be replaced.",
  "the page with the smallest count was brought in, yet to be used.",
  "the page with the longest count was brought in, yet to be used.", ],
    "answer": "the page with the smallest count to be replaced." },

    { "questionID": 24, 
  "questionText": "Which of the following class access protected and private members of other class?",
   "choices": ["Friend class",
  "Virtual class",
  "Main class",
  "None of these"],
    "answer": "Friend class" },

    { "questionID": 25, 
  "questionText": "What is a minimal super key in DBMS?",
   "choices": ["Candidate key",
  "Primary key",
  "Secondary key",
  "None of these", ],
    "answer": "Candidate key" },
]
